O'Brien, Leo W.; Papers apap267
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Correspondence, 1940-1966; Undated; 2; 1 cubic ft.
  - Corscadden, Paul-Correspondence-[RESTRICTED], 1952 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence), Folder 22)
  - Correspondence, 1953-1954 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence), Folder 23)
  - Correspondence, 1956-1957 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence), Folder 24)
  - Correspondence, 1958-1964 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence), Folder 25)
  - Correspondence, 1965-1966; Undated (Box 5 (2-Correspondence), Folder 26)
  - Dunn, James Ward-Correspondenc-[RESTRICTED], 1953; 1957 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence), Folder 27)
  - Ferony Walter-Correspondence-[RESTRICTED], 1954-1955 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence), Folder 28)
  - Floor Plans-Additional House Office Building, 1959 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence), Folder 29)
  - French, James H.-Correspondence, 1957-1958; 1960 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence), Folder 30)
  - Hamilton, Robert Anthony-Correspondence-[RESTRICTED], 1955 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence), Folder 31)
  - Hearst, Ronald A.-Correspondence-[RESTRICTED], 1954-1955 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence), Folder 32)
  - Kampfer, John B.-Correspondence-[RESTRICTED], 1957 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence), Folder 33)
  - Kane, John Peter-Correspondence-[RESTRICTED], 1950; 1952 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence), Folder 34)
  - LaFond, John Allen-Correspondence-[RESTRICTED], 1955 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence), Folder 35)
  - Meary, John Patrick-Correspondence - [RESTRICTED], 1953-1954; 1957 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence), Folder 36)
  - Merchant Marine Academy-Correspondence-[RESTRICTED], 1965-1966 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence), Folder 37)
  - Merchant Marine-Correspondence, 1966 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence), Folder 38)
  - Miscellaneous-Awards, Pictures, etc., 1957-1958; Undated (Box 5 (2-Correspondence), Folder 39)
  - Miscellaneous-Correspondence, 1964-1965 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence), Folder 40)
  - Murphy, Robert Paul-Correspondence-[RESTRICTED], 1955-1956 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence), Folder 41)
  - O'Brien, Leo W.-Correspondence, 1953; 1956-1962 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence), Folder 42)
  - O'Brien, Leo W.-Correspondence, 1954-1955; 1959 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence), Folder 43)
  - O'Brien, Leo W.-Correspondence, 1956-1957; 1959 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence), Folder 44)
  - O'Brien, Leo W.-Correspondence, 1962-1963 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence), Folder 45)
  - O'Brien, Leo W.-Correspondence, 1964 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence), Folder 46)
  - O'Brien, Leo W.-Correspondence, 1964-1965 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence), Folder 47)
  - O'Brien, Leo W.-Correspondence, 1965-1966 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence), Folder 48)
  - Office-Correspondence, 1952 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence), Folder 49)
  - Office-Correspondence, 1952-1953 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence), Folder 50)
  - Office-Correspondence, 1955-1958 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence), Folder 51)
  - Office-Correspondence, 1958 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence), Folder 52)
  - Office-Correspondence, 1959 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence), Folder 53)
  - Office-Correspondence, 1960 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence), Folder 54)
  - Office-Correspondence, 1961 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence), Folder 55)
  - Office-Correspondence, 1962 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence), Folder 56)
  - Office-Correspondence, 1963 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence), Folder 57)
  - Office-Correspondence, 1964 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence), Folder 58)
  - Office-Correspondence, 1964-1965 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence), Folder 59)
  - Office-Correspondence, 1965-1966 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence), Folder 60)
  - Robinson, Edward Charles-Correspondence, 1954-1955 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence), Folder 61)
  - Staff Appointments, etc.-Correspondence, 1965-1966 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence), Folder 62)
  - Tauhey, Robert J.-Correspondence, 1955 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence), Folder 63)
  - West Point-Correspondence-[RESTRICTED], 1950-1952 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence), Folder 64)
  - West Point-Correspondence-[RESTRICTED], 1952-1953 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence), Folder 65)
  - West Point-Correspondence, 1953-1955 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence), Folder 66)
  - West Point-Correspondence, 1955-1957 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence), Folder 67)
  - West Point-Correspondence-[RESTRICTED], 1963-1966 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence), Folder 68)
  - West Point-Correspondence-[RESTRICTED], 1964-1966 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence), Folder 69)
- Communications, 1942-1966; Undated; 3; 1.25 cubic ft.
  This series contains news clippings, official papers of Congress, press releases, office papers including cadet information, and remarks and speeches. There are several reel-to-reel tapes and 16mm films documenting Representative O'Brien's speeches or comments. In addition, there is supplemental correspondence in some files.
  - Admission Day Celebration Remarks, Hawaii, 1959 (Reel 1)
  - Capital Correspondent, Remote from Republican State Convention, 1950 September 06 (Record 1)
  - Clippings, 1953-1954; 1957-1959; 1963; 1966 (Box 6 (3-Communications), Folder 1)
  - Clippings, 1954-1966 (Box 6 (3-Communications), Folder 2)
  - Clippings, 1954; 1956; 1959-1960; 1963; 1965-1966 (Box 6 (3-Communications), Folder 3)
  - Clippings, 1954; 1956; 1958; 1962; 1966 (Box 6 (3-Communications), Folder 4)
  - Committee on Interior and Insular Affairs "Tributes", 1966 (Box 6 (3-Communications), Folder 5)
  - Congress Papers 77th Congress, 1942 (Box 6 (3-Communications), Folder 6)
  - Congress Papers 83rd Congress, 1953-1954 (Box 6 (3-Communications), Folder 7)
  - Congress Papers 84th Congress, 1955-1956 (Box 6 (3-Communications), Folder 8)
  - Congress Papers 85th Congress, 1958-1959 (Box 6 (3-Communications), Folder 9)
  - Congress Papers 86th Congress, 1959-1960 (Box 6 (3-Communications), Folder 10-11)
  - Congress Papers-Miscellaneous, 1959-1961 (Box 6 (3-Communications), Folder 12)
  - Congress Papers 87th Congress, 1961-1962 (Box 6 (3-Communications), Folder 13)
  - Congress Papers 88th Congress, 1963-1964 (Box 6 (3-Communications), Folder 14)
  - Congress Papers 89th Congress, 1965-1966 (Box 6 (3-Communications), Folder 15)
  - Hagerty, Jim, Undated; genreform: 16 mm film (Film 1)
  - News and You, Serial #1, Played on Saturday, February 11, 1956; genreform: 16 mm film ends at 13:34 (Film 2)
  - News and You, Serial #2, Played on Saturday, February 25, ca. 1956; genreform: 16 mm film ends at 14:06 (Film 3)
  - News and You, Serial #3, Played on Saturday, March 18, ca. 1956; genreform: 16 mm film ends at 14:30 (Film 4)
  - News and You, Serial #4, Played on Sunday, March 25, ca. 1956; genreform: 16 mm film ends at 13:48 (Film 5)
  - Office Papers, 1950-1957; 1964-1965 (Box 6 (3-Communications), Folder 16)
  - Office Papers-Cadet Information, 1963-1966 (Box 6 (3-Communications), Folder 17)
  - Office Papers-Cadet Information, 1953-1956; 1966 (Box 6 (3-Communications), Folder 18)
  - Office Papers-Miscellaneous, 1940; 1965-1966 (Box 6 (3-Communications), Folder 19)
  - Pamphlets on Alaska, 1959 (Box 6 (3-Communications), Folder 20)
  - Press Releases, 1952; 1954; 1958; 1964; 1966 (Box 6 (3-Communications), Folder 21)
  - Report from Washington, 1965 May 09 (Reel 2)
  - Report from Washington, ca. 1965 June 6 (Reel 3)
  - Report from Washington, ca. 1965 August 1 (Reel 4)
  - Report from Washington, 1965 August 25 (Reel 5)
  - Report from Washington, Undated (Reel 6)
  - Rep. O'Brien, 1960 March 10 (Reel 7)
  - Report from Washington, 1964 (Reel 8)
  - Speeches and Remarks, 1958; Undated (Box 6 (3-Communications), Folder 22)
  - Speeches and Remarks, 1965; Undated (Box 6 (3-Communications), Folder 23)